{"data":{"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"4112","name":"The Keep","address":"140 Cadillac Sq","zipcode":"48226","owner":"Dena Hamilton","licenseNumber":"069402","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","mostRecentLicenseDate":"4/30/2018","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":null,"reviewFrequencyDays":"180.0","geom":"0101000020E6100000702EC09CCBC254C0E82B9176692A4540","inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"44168","establishmentid":"4112","name":"The Keep","inspectionDate":"2018-11-23T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"131","pcount":"1","pfcount":"0","ccount":"1","criticalcount":"1","noncritical":"1","correctedcritical":"1","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"44168","inspectionDate":"11/23/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4112","name":"The Keep","violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not clean","subProblem":"","location":"BASEMENT (BAR)","subLocation":"At the Drain","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean"},{"inspectionid":"44168","inspectionDate":"11/23/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4112","name":"The Keep","violationCode":"3-301.11","violationDescription":"(A) To prevent food contamination FOOD EMPLOYEES shall properly wash their      hands.\r\n(B) FOOD EMPLOYEES may not contact exposed, READY-TO-EAT FOOD with      their bare hands and shall use suitable UTENSILS such as deli tissue,       spatulas, tongs, single-use gloves, or dispensing EQUIPMENT. (P)\r\n(C) FOOD EMPLOYEES shall minimize bare hand and arm contact with exposed     FOOD that is not in a READY-TO-EAT form. (Pf)\r\n\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Ready-to-eat food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Handled with bare hands","subProblem":"","location":"BAR ( FIRST FLOOR)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-11-23T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Suitable utensils or single-use gloves are to be utilized."}]},{"inspectionid":"42168","establishmentid":"4112","name":"The Keep","inspectionDate":"2018-05-10T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"87","pcount":"0","pfcount":"3","ccount":"1","criticalcount":"3","noncritical":"1","correctedcritical":"3","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"42168","inspectionDate":"5/10/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4112","name":"The Keep","violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"quaternary ammonia","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"Missing Test strips","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-06-06T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide as required"},{"inspectionid":"42168","inspectionDate":"5/10/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4112","name":"The Keep","violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\r\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\r\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \r\n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\r\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"disposable, paper towels","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"BAR","subLocation":"All Handsink","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-05-10T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide"},{"inspectionid":"42168","inspectionDate":"5/10/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4112","name":"The Keep","violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"floors","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"In the Basement","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-06-06T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"inspectionid":"42168","inspectionDate":"5/10/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4112","name":"The Keep","violationCode":"5-205.11","violationDescription":"(A) A HANDWASHING SINK shall be maintained so that it is accessible at all times for EMPLOYEE use and used for no other purpose. (Pf)\r\n(B)  An automatic handwashing facility shall be used in accordance with manufacturer's instructions. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Handwashing sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not easily accessible","subProblem":"Items stored In","location":"STORAGE ROOM","subLocation":"In the Handsink","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-05-10T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Remove items from handsink.  Do not store items at handsink."}]},{"inspectionid":"39860","establishmentid":"4112","name":"The Keep","inspectionDate":"2017-09-07T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"130","pcount":"1","pfcount":"1","ccount":"0","criticalcount":"2","noncritical":"0","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"39860","inspectionDate":"9/7/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4112","name":"The Keep","violationCode":"3-603.11","violationDescription":"If an animal FOOD such as  beef, EGGS, FISH, lamb, milk, pork, POULTRY, or shellfish is served or sold raw, undercooked, or without otherwise being processed to eliminate pathogens, either in a READY-TO-EAT form or as an ingredient in another READY-TO-EAT FOOD, the PERMIT HOLDER shall inform CONSUMERS of the significantly increased RISK of consuming such FOODS, by using menu advisories, brochures, lable statements, table tents, placards, or other effective written means. (Pf)\r\nFOOD LAW SEC 6149\r\n...The food establishment may provide the following statement on selection information so that it is made pulblicly available: \"Ask your server about menu items that are cooked to order or served raw.  Consuming raw or undercooked, meats, poultry, shellfish, or eggs may increase your risk of foodborne illness.\"\r\nThe statements must be in a minimum of 11 point font and in a color that provides a clear contrast to background.\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Menu advisories","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"MENU(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"inspectionid":"39860","inspectionDate":"9/7/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4112","name":"The Keep","violationCode":"4-602.11","violationDescription":"(A) Equipment FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be cleaned:     \r\n  (1) Except as specified in ¶ (B) of this section, before each use with a different   type of raw animal FOOD such as beef, FISH, lamb, pork, or POULTRY; (P)   \r\n  (2) Each time there is a change from working with raw FOODS to working with   READY-TO-EAT FOODS; (P)   \r\n  (3) Between uses with raw fruits and vegetables and with POTENTIALLY   HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD);   (P)   \r\n  (4) Before using or storing a FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING   DEVICE; (P) and   \r\n  (5) At any time during the operation when contamination may have occurred. (P)\r\n(B) Subparagraph (A)(1) of this section does not apply if the FOOD-CONTACT SURFACE or UTENSIL is in contact with a succession of different raw animal FOODS each requiring a higher cooking temperature as specified under § 3-401.11 than the previous FOOD, such as preparing raw FISH followed by cutting raw poultry on the same cutting board.   \r\n(C) Except as specified in ¶ (D) of this section, if used with POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD), EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be cleaned throughout the day at least every 4 hours. (P)   \r\n(D) Except when dry cleaning methods are used as specified under § 4-603.11, surfaces of UTENSILS and EQUIPMENT contacting FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be cleaned:     \r\n  (1)   At any time when contamination may have occurred;\r\n  (2)   At least every 24 hours for iced tea dispensers and CONSUMER self-service UTENSILS such as tongs, scoops, or ladles;\r\n  (3) Before restocking CONSUMER self-service EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS such as condiment dispensers and display containers; and\r\n  (4) In EQUIPMENT such as ice bins and BEVERAGE dispensing nozzles and   enclosed components of EQUIPMENT such as ice makers, cooking oil storage   tanks and distribution lines, BEVERAGE and syrup dispensing lines or tubes,   coffee bean grinders, and water vending EQUIPMENT:\r\n     (a) At a frequency specified by the manufacturer, or\r\n     (b) Absent manufacturer specifications, at a frequency necessary to preclude      accumulation of soil or mold.","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"36277","establishmentid":"4112","name":"The Keep","inspectionDate":"2016-08-25T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"121","pcount":"0","pfcount":"2","ccount":"0","criticalcount":"2","noncritical":"0","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"36277","inspectionDate":"8/25/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4112","name":"The Keep","violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"quaternary ammonia","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide as required"},{"inspectionid":"36277","inspectionDate":"8/25/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4112","name":"The Keep","violationCode":"3-603.11","violationDescription":"If an animal FOOD such as  beef, EGGS, FISH, lamb, milk, pork, POULTRY, or shellfish is served or sold raw, undercooked, or without otherwise being processed to eliminate pathogens, either in a READY-TO-EAT form or as an ingredient in another READY-TO-EAT FOOD, the PERMIT HOLDER shall inform CONSUMERS of the significantly increased RISK of consuming such FOODS, by using menu advisories, brochures, lable statements, table tents, placards, or other effective written means. (Pf)\r\nFOOD LAW SEC 6149\r\n...The food establishment may provide the following statement on selection information so that it is made pulblicly available: \"Ask your server about menu items that are cooked to order or served raw.  Consuming raw or undercooked, meats, poultry, shellfish, or eggs may increase your risk of foodborne illness.\"\r\nThe statements must be in a minimum of 11 point font and in a color that provides a clear contrast to background.\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Menu advisories","subItem":"for raw or undercooked food(s)/ingredient(s) eggs","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"MENU(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."}]}]}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"4112"}}